<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chandra Harsha Jupalli</title>
    <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chandra Harsha Jupalli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 14:34:07 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.chandraharsha111.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS,API Specification,Jenkins and OAUTH </title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/apis_and_ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 14:34:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/apis_and_ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>CI CD Jenkins, Swagger, API concepts, Git  Git commands API best practices Swagger Jenkins aws-basics-dzone Sidecar Shell scripting curl oAuth1 and OAuth2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Oriented Design, Ruby, Kubernetes, JavaScript</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/ruby-js-kubernetes-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 19:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/ruby-js-kubernetes-design/</guid>
      <description>Java Script and design principles  SOLID principles Object Oriented design Object Models DOM Eloquent JS Book JS in browser Intro to JavaScript  Kubernetes, docker, Spinakker, Helm:  Docker Kubernetes Kubectl MiniKube Spinakker HelmCharts NewRelic  Ruby:  Ruby basics Ruby tutorial Ruby online org Tutorials point  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Learnings</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/technical-learnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 19:50:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/technical-learnings/</guid>
      <description>Assembly Management: Assembly: An &amp;ldquo;assembly&amp;rdquo; is a group of files, directories, and dependencies that are assembled into an archive format and distributed.
  WAR: A Web application Archive. For the purpose of this workshop, we will be using this in our tutorials.
  JAR: A Java Archive which include a Java specific manifest file. They are built on the ZIP (file format) and typically have the .jar file extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berkshire Annual reports summary</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/berkshire-annual-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 12:59:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/berkshire-annual-reports/</guid>
      <description>Bekshire Annual Reports Reading Notes Content from https://www.berkshirehathaway.com/reports.html 1999  Equity investors currently seem wildly optimistic in their expectations about future returns Share repurchases must be done only when business needs are take care of and only when the stock price is below its intrinsic value  2000 How to Think About Investing  The first investment primer was written by Aesop in 600 B.C. He said, &amp;lsquo;A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/software-development-resources-and-learnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 13:16:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/software-development-resources-and-learnings/</guid>
      <description>Blogs and websites  Dr Fawcett Dr KevinDu Bob Martin Martin Flower  Basic Introduction Videos  Virtualization Kubernetes Vs Docker Containers Vs VM Microservices Cloud Native Big data Kafka Helm Continuous Integration  Dev Resources  Ripgrep Brew Heap Analysis Host Hugo on GitHub Oh-my-zsh  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing resources</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/intesting-investing-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 11:56:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/intesting-investing-resources/</guid>
      <description>Books Investing  One up on WallStreet Beating the street Intelligent Investor Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits Principles RayDalio Business Adventures Dhandho Investor Making of American Capitalist Payback time Invested Random Walk down Wall Street Little book of common sense Investing Wealth of Nations The Snowball Genome Sapiens Ride of a lifetime Poor Charlies Almanack Value Investing from Graham to Buffet Great crash of 1929 Nick sleep letters Psychology of money  To read  100 to 1 in the stock market Margin of Safety How to avoid a climate disster Feeling good Titan Homo Deus 21 lessons for 21st century Real life MBA Stress Test Outsiders Richer Wiser Happier  Videos  Charlie Munger Warren Buffer Li Lu Monish Pobrai Lauren Templeton John Boggle  Financial websites and blogs  Economic Principles Ray Dalio Howard Marks memos Monish Pobrai AshwathDamodaran Phil Town Sanjay Bakshi Dataroma Value Line Magic Formula JL collins Mr Money Mustache Long River  Intersting blogs  Gates Notes Gap Minder USA facts  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common stocks and uncommon profits</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 23:17:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits/</guid>
      <description>Learnings from Phil Fisher Common stocks and uncommon profits  Finding an outstanding company and staying with it through fluctuations could be far more profitable than buying cheap and selling dear Even if depression occurs it could be short since FED or government can lower taxes, lower interest rates etc. which was not possible in 1929 Greatest investment reward comes to people those by luck or sense find an occasional company that can grow sales and profits far more than industry over years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:36:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>ACADEMIC PROJECTS GROUP NOTIFIER ANDROID APP [Java, PHP, Restful API, JSON, Firebase]  Created a user-friendly app that helps users in a group to share deadlines and notify team members about events Worked with Google API, Google Maps, Voice to text API, YouTube API, Async Tasks, Animations (Toxic Bakery) Utilized Firebase Cloud to authenticate users and stored group information in JSON format in Firebase  REMOTE CODE PUBLISHER [C++, WPF, Visual Studio]  Devised an application Remote Code Publisher that converts source code as web pages with embedded child links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chandra Harsha Jupalli</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:36:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Good Judgement comes from experience and experience comes from bad judgemement - Jim Horning Software Development Experience  Cerner Corporation, Software Engineer, 2018-Present  Responsible for driving API reviews across micro services to eliminate redundant API’s in Millennium an EHR product. Developed sidecar functionality, which casts SRV requests to HTTP, created docker images and deployed the service using Helm to Kubernetes. Gained experience working with CI-CD concepts using Jenkins Pipelines. Implemented UI using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery Data Table API to create responsive web pages, created endpoints in Spring MVC to add export functionality, implemented CRUD operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summaries and Investing Basics for Active Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/book-summaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 21:59:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/book-summaries/</guid>
      <description>Compound Interest is the eighth wonder of the world. He who understand it, earns it. He who does not pays it. Intelligent Investor   Stocks do well when inflation is moderate, bad when low, erratic when high inflation
  Treasury bonds with no tax to combat inflation like Public Provident Fund(India) - about 10%
  Adequate but not excessive diversification
  Have 25% in Bonds and rest in Stocks –(Cushion for emotional stability)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 17:35:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</guid>
      <description>Bird in the hand is worth two in the bush - Aesop 600BC Investing can simply be put as a process in which upon thorough analysis, promises safety of principal and adequate return. For anyone looking into investing understanding available categories, before thinking about available choices within those categories could help with rate of return expectations. Broadly speaking I think most investors have these following options available with them
 Commodities Currency Denominated Investments Productive Assets  Commodities: Gold, Silver, Oil, Cotton</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
