<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chandra Harsha Jupalli</title>
    <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chandra Harsha Jupalli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:35:28 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.chandraharsha111.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:36:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Work In progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chandra Harsha Jupalli</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:36:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Good Judgement comes from experience and experience comes from bad judgemement - Jim Horning Software Development Experience  Cerner Corporation, Software Engineer, 2018-Present  Responsible for driving API reviews across micro services to eliminate redundant API’s in Millennium an EHR product. Developed sidecar functionality, which casts SRV requests to HTTP, created docker images and deployed the service using Helm to Kubernetes. Gained experience working with CI-CD concepts using Jenkins Pipelines. Implemented UI using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery Data Table API to create responsive web pages, created endpoints in Spring MVC to add export functionality, implemented CRUD operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:35:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</guid>
      <description>Bird in the hand is worth two in the bush - 600BC Investing can simply be put as a process in which upon thorough analysis, promises safety of principal and adequate return. For anyone looking into investing understanding available categories, before you start thinking about choices available within those categories could help with rate of return expectations and stay rational. Broadly speaking I think most investors have these following options</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
