<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chandra Harsha Jupalli</title>
    <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chandra Harsha Jupalli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 13:16:34 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/software-development-resources-and-learnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 13:16:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/software-development-resources-and-learnings/</guid>
      <description>Blogs and websites  Dr Fawcett Dr KevinDu Bob Martin Martin Flower  Videos  Virtualization Kubernetes Vs Docker Containers Vs VM Microservices Cloud Native Big data Kafka Helm Continuous Integration  Dev Resources  Ripgrep Brew Heap Analysis Host Hugo on GitHub  Heap Terms  Xmx - maximum memory allocation pool for a Java virtual machine (JVM) Xms - initial memory allocation pool for JVM Xmn - young generation heap size  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing resources</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/intesting-investing-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 11:56:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/intesting-investing-resources/</guid>
      <description>Books Few of my interesting reads  One up on WallStreet Intelligent Investor Beating the street Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits Dhandho Investor Random Walk down Wall Street Business Adventures Making of American Capitalist Payback time Invested Principles RayDalio Little book of common sense Investing  To Read:  Capitalism in America Other Half of macroeconomics Wealth of Nations  Videos  Charlie Munger Warren Buffer Li Lu Monish Pobrai Monish Pobrai Lauren Templeton John Boggle  Financial websites and Blogs  Economic Principles Ray Dalio Howard Marks memos Dataroma value Line Monish Pobrai AshwathDamodaran JL collins Mr Money Mustache Magic Formula Phil Town Sanjay Bakshi  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common stocks and uncommon profits</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 23:17:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits/</guid>
      <description>Writing this blog post on my key learnings from one of the best investing book for Active Investors Common stocks and uncommon profits  Finding an outstanding company and staying with it through fluctuations could be far more profitable than buying cheap and selling dear Even if depression occurs it could be short since FED or government can lower taxes, lower interest rates etc. which was not possible in 1929 Greatest investment reward comes to people those by luck or sense find an occasional company that can grow sales and profits far more than industry over years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summaries and Investing Basics for Active Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/book-summaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 21:59:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/book-summaries/</guid>
      <description>Compound Interest is the eighth wonder of the world. He who understand it, earns it. He who does not pays it. Intelligent Investor   Stocks do well when inflation is moderate, bad when low, erratic when high inflation
  Treasury bonds with no tax to combat inflation like Public Provident Fund(India) - about 10%
  Adequate but not excessive diversification
  Have 25% in Bonds and rest in Stocks –(Cushion for emotional stability)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:35:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</guid>
      <description>Bird in the hand is worth two in the bush - 600BC Investing can simply be put as a process in which upon thorough analysis, promises safety of principal and adequate return. For anyone looking into investing understanding available categories, before we start thinking about the choices available within those categories could help us with rate of return expectations and staying rational. Broadly speaking I think most of the investors have these following options available with them</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
