<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chandra Harsha Jupalli</title>
    <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chandra Harsha Jupalli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 23:17:22 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Common stocks and uncommon profits</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 23:17:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits/</guid>
      <description>Writing this blog post on my key learnings from just this book, since I felt this is one of the best investing book for Active Investors Common stocks and uncommon profits  Finding an outstanding company and staying with it through fluctuations could be far more profitable than buying cheap and selling dear Even if depression occurs it could be short since FED or government can lower taxes, lower interest rates etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Summaries and Investing Basics for Active Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/book-summaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 21:59:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/book-summaries/</guid>
      <description>Compound Interest is the eighth wonder of the world. He who understand it, earns it. He who does not pays it. Intelligent Investor   Stocks do well when inflation is moderate, bad when low, erratic when high inflation
  Treasury bonds with no tax to combat inflation like Public Provident Fund(India) - about 10%
  Adequate but not excessive diversification
  Have 25% in Bonds and rest in Stocks –(Cushion for emotional stability)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Investing</title>
      <link>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:35:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chandraharsha111.com/posts/thoughts-on-investing/</guid>
      <description>Bird in the hand is worth two in the bush - 600BC Investing can simply be put as a process in which upon thorough analysis, promises safety of principal and adequate return. For anyone looking into investing understanding available categories, before you start thinking about choices available within those categories could help with rate of return expectations and stay rational. Broadly speaking I think most investors have these following options</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
